sinrex.com 2015-10-10

# Privacy Policy

**Sinrex.com** recognizes the importance of protecting your online privacy. This Privacy Statement explains our views and practices concerning privacy while visiting our site, and how they may affect you as a user of our affiliate program.

"You" or "Your" means you as a participant in or as a user of the **Sinrex.com** website. "We" or "Our" or "Us" means **Sinrex.com** and its subsidiaries.

All information transmitted, printed or otherwise submitted to **Sinrex.com** will be deemed to be the property of **Sinrex.com** and **Sinrex.com** is free to use such information for any lawful purpose as detailed herein.

We reserve the right to release any such information to law enforcement or other government officials only in order to comply with the law.

### **Section 1**

**Collected Information**

We automatically collect and/or track the following:

  1. Information knowingly provided by you through our on-line forms, registration forms, surveys, and/or other entries, such as email addresses, personal, financial or demographic information;
  2. Information, user specific or aggregate, on what pages our visitors access;
  3. And E-mail addresses of customers that communicate with **Sinrex.com** via e-mail.

### Section 2

**Use of Data Collected**

Information collected by us may be added to our databases and used for future marketing, e-mails or postal mailings regarding site updates, new products and services, upcoming events, and/or status of online accounts. By using this site, you agree that you may be contacted in any manner mentioned in this section.

### Section 3

**Our Right to Contact You**

We reserve the right to contact you regarding your account status and changes to purchase agreements, privacy policy, or any other policies or agreements relevant to you.

### Section 4

**Our Right to Change**

We reserve the right to change this policy at any time by updating or revising our privacy policy or by posting the changes online at our site.

### Section 5

**Our Contact Information**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact us via email sent to: **webmaster** [at] **Sinrex.com**.

### Section 6

**Anti Spam Policy. Can-Spam Act Compliance**

**Sinrex.com** is dedicated to ensuring compliance with the 'Can-Spam Act', which took effect January 1, 2004. You may receive email from **Sinrex.com** in the following circumstances:

  1. Acknowledging your purchase request has been received and requesting additional action requests for additional information to support your current application.
  2. Response to your inquiries regarding the status of your order.
  3. Thanking you for your valued business.
  4. Advertisements for our products, services, changes in services, new product availability

As a visitor of **Sinrex.com** and consumer of **Sinrex** products,you must accept the terms and agreements of our Terms of Service and Privacy Policy.
